

☑ noelcedrix@yahoo.com

3 0995-295-6110

A Obando, Bulacan

m www.linkedin.com/in/noelcedrixjoaquin

SKILLS



LANGUAGES

- Filipino
- English

INTERESTS

- Anime
- Toy Photography
- Tekken

Noel Cedrix Joaquin

Application Developer

Application Developer with over 2 years of experience in areas such as Production Support and Web Development. Team player with exposure in working with local and international colleagues. Highly motivated in learning new tools and technologies.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

L1 Production Support

Accenture Inc. – Cigna Bruin

06/2021 - Present

- Technologies utilized: Python, SQL, Domino Data Lab, ServiceNow, Confluence, GitHub, Dash, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Intercom and Dynatrace
- Primary contact of support to over 1700 data scientists and engineers within Analytics Platform in helping solve problems related to Domino Data Lab, data/platform access, and code.
- Create and maintain existing Confluence pages that are being used by all employees of Cigna utilizing the Analytics Platform.
- Develop proof-of-concept ticket dashboard using Python for metrics reporting that will be consumed by managers and stakeholders.
- Design and integrate custom bot within Domino Data Lab using Intercom to assist users in resolving common types of issues without submitting a ticket.
- Collaborate with engineering team in setting up Dynatrace synthetic alerts to proactively monitor outages within Analytics Platform.
- Demonstrate newly found issues, workaround, and best practices within Analytics Platform during bi-weekly open forums.
- Created learning materials and provided trainings to onboard 4 new resources within L1 Support and Site Reliability Engineering Team.

Web Developer

Accenture Inc. – Cigna Census UI

03/2021 - 04/2021

- Technologies utilized: C#, ASP.NET Core MVC, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap and MS SQL Server
- Codes according to design specification to produce required functionality.
- Research and implementation of database integration.
- Provide support to senior developers during testing and provision of test data.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering

Adamson University

06/2013 - 01/2020

TRAININGS

Data and Analytics Bootcamp

Accenture Inc. 01/2021 – 03/2021

Complete Python Bootcamp: From Zero to Hero in Python

Udemy 06/2020